all right I figured out how to use an
online whiteboard somewhat so I'm going
to walk you through the Netflix of apps
with actual audio hopefully so I just
want to explain how Netflix works just
in case you didn't know but more
importantly how to gather tech works
similarly and yet completely magically
different I'm done right needs more than
that
okay so Netflix works like this users
pay approximately $10 per month per
account and personally and for that
money the user gets infinite access to
their catalogue of films cat thumbs all
the cat films even one catalog of films
we are the Netflix of apps so for $10
per member is where a co-op they get
unlimited access to our catalog apps now
Netflix has their licensed content and
they have original content so this would
be things like Disney Star Wars original
content would be like sensei and
stranger things
they started out just licensing content
but they had so much money from their
for profit from people paying $10 a
month that they for the purpose of
profit decided to put body into new
projects that they thought their
membership would like and some of them
have been successes and some of them not
so much but that is their two options we
also can license content or create
original so let's say we
license Yelp to work with our other apps
and I some food network app that we like
we can also create our own
so the idea Cafe would be one that we
would create which is what I'm working
on currently on its own YouTube channel
we could create a childcare app one big
huge difference is that Netflix if
Disney decides they're gonna create
their own streaming video which they
have decided and no longer want to
license to Netflix Netflix is not
allowed to just move licensed over to
original content they could recreate
generic ice princess but nobody is going
to watch it they cannot just move
licensed content to original we however
if Yelp is too expensive can just
recreate a restaurant slash service
rating system if the food network is too
expensive for us to license we can
recreate our own food program so we in
fact the point is to eventually have
almost all original content and less
license the content is so amazing and
created for purpose instead of profit
also Netflix once sense8 is there once
stranger things or even frozen is
released it is released in its final
format they don't go back and change it
because they notice there's an error we
however because of how apps work can
create something and keep it continually
improving it and making it better and
better and better I don't know what
graphic could showcase that but like you
get what you get here it's like it's
released as its final star product
that's a star everyone whereas ours can
get infinitely better continually by
increasing it their decision
are all made because they're a company
for profit because we are owned and run
by our members who the reason they are
there is so they can use the apps the
apps are created not for profit not for
how much money we can make off of them
but once we break even once it makes
sense the threshold is met we're
creating for purpose the purpose of our
childcare app is to create better
childcare not to make more money but
just like Netflix and no one's forced to
come on board and use Netflix right the
government doesn't say you have to pay
$10 a month this is a tax and you happen
to get to get a catalogue of films from
it we also the only way people are gonna
come on board and want to use our apps
is if we create better apps
then what is out there for free if we
create better apps than when it's out
there for more than $10 a month well if
we have that right now basically nobody
wouldn't want to jump on board if we had
a catalog of apps lets you eat healthy
like you spend less money to get more
helped you interact with your neighbors
and and found community in a way that
was empowering and helped you everyone
would want that but we're not forcing
anyone to come on board just like
Netflix not everyone's gonna like Disney
not everyone's gonna like sense8 or
stranger things their mandate is that
there's something for everyone right
there's something for your kid there's
something for you they have to keep
releasing new content because once
you've seen with the exception of Disney
that your kid will watch all the time
every day
once you've seen sunset you're not
necessarily gonna keep watching it you
wouldn't pay $10 a month for the same
catalog continually unless it was a
infinite catalog however we can actually
just create we're not going to create
new life-changing apps every month but
once we have the foundation of the ones
we need we can improve them but we don't
need to keep recreating them unless
there's a there's a need for it unless
there is something we miss something
else that we need to create but we're
not we also not every app is going to be
used by every member
we're gonna have something for everyone
but not every app is gonna be for
everyone just like Netflix doesn't worry
about is everybody gonna launch says
sensei they want enough people to watch
it that it breaks even we are not even
creating it they have to create with the
an idea of what their user wants but
you'll be really hard for them to pull
their audience and be like who would
watch sense they'd try explaining that
to people so there's 80 people who are
born at the same time and they all can
like go in each other's mind you're like
well if it's good I'll watch it that's
basically all so does everyone want a
food out well yes if it's good if I can
use it if it's user friendly and
beautiful and functions absolutely I
want it and so together we can create
apps that don't just impact our own life
also impact the system we can understand
climate change we can reduce poverty we
can do things without leaving them up to
the government and for-profit
corporations because Netflix is not
going to come on board and solve climate
change together tech is going to because
we want it to be solved we're gonna
solve the childcare issue and I don't
mean it's just gonna get solved
instantly we're gonna start with how do
we improve it how do we keep improving
it how do we keep making it better how
do we create a new system that everybody
has an improvement
not everyone has a perfect life but
everyone keeps improving and so that was
how the Netflix of apps called together
tech is what we're gonna create together
and I hope that showcased a bit more
than just me speaking my beautiful
beautiful whiteboard what it is we're
gonna create thank you